<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ayyappa App</string>
    <string name="google_place_api">AIzaSyCDjVe3vsBBHqgnGqnBvtGJGGd_wmY5yXA</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="who_can"><center>WHO can do it?</center></string>
    <string name="deeksha_rules">Males: Any one can do it.
Females: Below age 10 and above 50 can observe deeksha</string>

    <string name="when">when?</string>
    <string name="deeksha_rules1">It is usually observed during the Mandalam
        (which usually falls between Nov 2nd week and Sankranthi).
        Mandalam starts on first day of Kartika Masam (as per Kerala Calendar)</string>

    <string name="where">where?</string>
    <string name="deeksha_rules2">Mala Dharana can be done in any temple.
        It is usually done by Guruswami (who had been to Sabrimala 18 times) or the priest at the
        temple.Deeksha will be ended after returning home from Sabarimala.
        Mala should not be removed in Pamba or Sannidham.</string>

    <string name="What_to_do">what to do?</string>
    <string name="deeksha_rules3">• Take bath in early morning and evening with cold water.
         (Clarify usage of Soap and Shampoo from your guru Swamy).\n\n
        • Daily visit temple.\n\n
        • Take bath in early morning and evening with cold water.\n\n
        • Do the pooja twice a day, morning (before sun rise) and evening (after sunset).\n\n
        • Do your regular daily pooja followed by Ashotharam (108 namas) to Ganesh,Subramanyam, Durga and Ayyappan.\n\n
        • Chant Hairivarasanam only after evening Pooja.\n\n
        • No need for cooked Prasadam every day. Fruits as Naivedyam for Ayyappan are OK.\n\n
        • Take bath as soon you come home in the evening from work.\n
        • Wear only Black Dress.\n\n
        • You should never take the mala out.\n\n
        • Use fresh clothes every day. So, have two pairs of black dress and wash them every day.\n\n
        • No Breakfast.\n\n
        • Lunch: Should take fresh cooked food before noon. No left overs from previous day.\n\n
        • Dinner: Should take light food like, upma, idli.\n\n
        • No onion,garlic, egg or meat products.\n\n
        • Outside food should be completely avoided.\n\n
        • If anyone calls you for Annadanam you should not refuse the invitation.\n\n
          Make sure they should have prepared the meal after taking bath etc.\n\n
        • When you or your spouse is preparing meal, make sure you clean the stove before cooking.\n\n

</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="refresh_token">Get Fresh Token</string>
    <string name="desc_google_icon">Google Logo</string>
    <string name="title_text">Google Sign-In\nQuickstart</string>
    <string name="signed_out">Signed out</string>
    <string name="signed_in_fmt">Signed in as: %s</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
      <string name="quickstart_message">Click the SUBSCRIBE TO NEWS button below to subscribe to the
        news topic. Messages sent to the news topic will be received. The LOG TOKEN button logs the
        InstanceID token to logcat.</string>
    <string name="subscribe_to_news">Subscribe To News</string>
    <string name="log_token">Log Token</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id" translatable="false">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <string name="msg_subscribed">Subscribed to news topic</string>
    <string name="msg_token_fmt" translatable="false">InstanceID Token: %s</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name" translatable="true">News</string>
</resources>
